

Student Profile

20-year-old computer science major. Currently in 3rd year. Front-End developer and UI-UX designer. Working to be a full-stack developer and product designer. Always ecstatic and enthusiastic to better myself and constantly striving to learn more. Aspiring author.

I would be interested in internships relating to front end development and UI-UX Design

Areas of Expertise

- HTML
- CSS
- Java
- JavaScript
- R
- Python
- Content Writing

Reach me at:

a.manasa0601@gmail.com

Work Experience

UI-UX LEAD

DSC, VIT-AP | JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- Assisting core team in UI-UX solutions
- Pitching designs
- Understand and work towards the design needs of any project

PRESIDENT

ENGLISH LITERARY ASSOCIATION, VIT - AP | AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

- Lead club to organize events
- Manage a team of 10+ students
- Be an integral part in the decision making of the club

ASSOCIATE AND TEAM LEADER

AIESEC IN AMRAVATI | AUGUST 2020 - JULY 2021

- Generated leads for exchanges
- Managed International Relations from Brazil, Austria and Egypt
- Cracked University Relation with VIT-AP
- Managed a team for 6 months

Education History

VELLORE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY. AP

B.TECH COMPUTER SCIENCE | JULY 2019 - PRESENT

VELOCIITY

HIGH SCHOOL | JULY 2017 - APRIL 2019

Projects

- Redesigned the GDSC VIT-AP page for both desktop and mobile
- Currently working on a medical chatbot called AI-d
- Automatic Watering System based on all contributing factors using Arduino Uno